Good day.  There have
been a lot of
spring rains lately, and it's
fitting—they've
led to an
exceptionally bountiful
mushroom hunting season.  I take great
pleasure in wandering
through places that were
once burned,
finding wrinkles
hidden among the
ash and soot.
Today I wanted to
share what I've
been up to, and also
give a little
tour of my
plot.  Like in my
last video, I didn't
quite get my
hands on this one.  I
plan to show everything with the
camera around the
12th minute of the video, so
you can
skip straight to that if you want.
Personally, I get
a lot of satisfaction
from creating longer
videos that cover a
larger part of my
day.  For me,
a big part of this
video is
about where I live, in a
broader sense,
because I think a lot of
locals would agree:
when you live in a
place like this, the valley
is an extension of
your home.  This time of
year, I love to prepare an
aromatic blend of
my favorite
flowers and scents.  You
can add your
favorite ingredients
and leave it on the
stove as a floating
bouquet, or put it
on a slow fire
to make it smell wonderful all around
.  This is such a
simple and beautiful
way to honor
spring.  Maybe it's
noticeable on my
face, but
wedding preparations have
been ramping up lately
.  I'm getting married.  By
the time this video
comes out, my
wedding will be
just a week away.  So
I have a lot of things to do.  And
because of that, I didn't get much
sleep last
night.  I have to admit,
this
happens sometimes.  And, uh, I'm
a little tired.  But
I knew: the one thing that
always brings me back
to life when I
feel exhausted
is time spent
among flowers and
walks in new
places for me.  If you
hear the sounds in the
background: Luke and I
collected all these pine
cones and bits of
moss to put
in
solar-powered lanterns as
gifts for everyone.  And the
kitten plays with
all this.  Thanks to
popular support for
the name Movi, in honor of the movi
tree, we
named the kitten Movi.
You could say that "
mauvi" is probably
more correct, but "
movi" is easier for many people
to pronounce.  So
we settled on
this option.  And yes,
she is a real
troublemaker.  She has
so much
energy now.  She is learning
to control her
paws and is simply
enjoying
life to the fullest.  And it
really inspires me to
do the same.  So, while
walking among the
wildflowers, I
found a small
piece of wood in
the shape of a diamond.    I
remember being so
excited that I
sent a picture of it to
my fiancé because
I thought it was the
most amazing thing, because there
was a hole in the middle.
Hmm, perfect size
to look through
.  According to
fairy tales,
there is a so-called "
witch stone"
- a stone with a
natural hole
in the middle.  Legend
has it that if you look
into this hole, you
will receive an invitation
to look through a
portal into the land of fairies.
Although it wasn't a rock
but a piece of wood,
it looked
like a real
potential portal
to the fairies to me.  So my
inner child
was very, very
happy with this
find.  It was a
real treasure.  She is
so noisy.
Sorry if she kept
interrupting
this story.  Why are you
so noisy?  Anyway
, I took it
and put it in my
pocket so I wouldn't
lose it, buttoned the pocket
, but
when I returned from my
walk, I
couldn't find it.
It was no longer in
my pocket.  I was
so disappointed because I
thought it was such a
fun little
treasure to
bring home.  But
yeah, I think maybe the
fairies are playing with me,
because I really wanted to
show you that
little portal.  This is the
tragedy of the
magic stone
that I found and
lost under
mysterious circumstances.
So, here it is.  Here's a
story that would have
captivated me at the age of
seven.
I think when we
revisit
things from our childhood or
favorite activities, we
often add a layer of
self-criticism to what we
do.  And this
prevents us from
truly
relaxing and
enjoying ourselves
.  So I
think a great
practice is to just
let it go.  I know
that as a child I
looked at the world with
such wonder and
admiration.  And
rediscovering that magic is
very powerful.  And I
think if we
let go of
worrying about what
others might think,
or what another part of
us might think about
that childish part, we
can discover
so much more of what
we truly
love.  You look for
little treasures or
interesting corners that you would
n't notice if you
perceived the hike only
as a workout or
some mandatory
task.  And I'm sitting here
watching
my bread come in.
I think it's almost
ready to bake.
My whole family
comes to visit,
even my grandmother from
Puerto Rico.  They
will all be here soon.  So
I wanted to bake them
bread to
celebrate the
meeting.
I haven't seen some of them in years.  This is what is
on the
agenda today.  And,
of course, there is no
greater treasure
I could give them at this
time of year than wrinkle
mushrooms, because they are very
mysterious and
amazing mushrooms that
grow in this
area in the spring.
Now I'm going to go make some
bread, put it in
the oven, and
I'll see you soon.  Mauvi, oh
my god, what have you done?
Here is the bread, and I can't
resist.  I have to
share with you
probably one of my
favorite, most
calming sounds
, and it's this sound.  I
thought it would be
worth showing you a
little tour of
our site today.  It's
difficult because I
have neighbors here, and they
live much
closer than where I
lived before.  So I don't
want to show their
houses, simply because
I would be
embarrassed to do so.
But I'll show you
a little bit of what it
looks like and
feels like here in the spring, because
it's a wonderful, very
romantic time, if I
can't find a better
description.  With all these
flowers, everything around
seems so
lush and green.
I won't be taking a tour of the garden just yet
.
Many of the wildflowers
I grow,
like calendula and
marigolds, really
bloom when it
gets warmer in the summer.
So I'll wait until then to
show you what I've
grown.  In the
meantime, I thought I'd
show you a few
short videos of what it's like
outside, although
I'll try not to
film the neighbors'
houses.  So, when you
walk out our
front door, the first thing you
see is a very
interesting art object.
Luke is building us an arch
for our wedding, and he's
trying to make
it out of aspen trees that burned down in
last year's fire.  He has
n't quite finished it yet
, but it looks
great.
There is a layer of gravel around the house
, which will help
protect it in the event of a
forest fire, which,
unfortunately, is quite likely
.  This little path
leads to the house, and my
dog ​​loves it very much
.  There are so many trees,
bushes, and flowers around, everything
looks so
luxurious.  It's hard
to believe that it
will be so dry here in a few months.  And here,
unfortunately,
the camera shakes again, because I
probably can't
stand still for a
second while I'm filming.
But yes, we don't have
paved roads.
Everything around is dirt
and quite dusty,
but he
likes it because it doesn't
hurt his paws.  And in the summer,
when the asphalt
usually gets too
hot, he can
safely walk on these
roads.  Fortunately, it
doesn't take that long to get to the city
.  Although you have to
travel a bit
.  We
have mobile
reception here, so we
use
the Internet via a
hotspot and hope to
connect
Starlink soon.  And here you see the
old
treehouse that my
fiancé Luke
built when he was a
little boy.
It stands on the plot of land of
my future
relatives.  I
think it's so sweet
that we can live so close to where
he grew up.
Living in the forest means
we have to take
extra
safety precautions because of wild
animals.  For example,
a bear had already
rummaged through our
trash several times, so we
had to look for new
solutions.  The trees are
full of squirrels and other
animals, and my dog
has to get used to
this constant
noise.  This place is completely
unlike where I
lived before, but I
love this
adventure full of
discoveries.
The most common plants growing on our
site are
delphiniums,
balsam root,
arnica, lupine,
claytonia, bellflowers,
as well as many
irga bushes.  And this list
can be continued
endlessly.  If you've
ever been
curious about
plants in your
area, I highly
recommend using a
mobile app
if you don't have access to
experts.  This is a great
way to start
learning what these
plants are.  You may be
surprised by what
grows near you.
I
used the
Picture This app before, it was
great for
identification and
gave me a starting
point for verifying
information.  The whole
area has such a
magical natural
fence.  It was built
to keep horses,
as it was a
converted barn
, and Luke's father kept
horses here.  We live
on a plot of
about an acre and are
connected to a
shared area
in the woods.  We have a few
neighbors and it's just
great.  They were all
so welcoming and
kind.  Starting a
new life here is so
exciting.  Sending
you all my love and
I hope you
enjoyed it.  And when
you see me
next time, I'll
be married.  So this is
really very
exciting.  Good night
, see you
soon.